<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-15" standalone="no"?><uc-export clientvers="11.0.0">
<DOCU name="PCK.AUTOMIC_APACHE_HTTPSERVER.PUB.DOC">
<HEADER state="1">
<Title>Package documentation</Title>
<ArchiveKey1/>
<ArchiveKey2/>
<OH_SubType/>
</HEADER>
<DOCU_Docu state="1" type="text">
<DOC><![CDATA[About Automic's Apache HTTP Server Package
================================
This package provides the integration with Apache HTTP Server. The Apache HTTP Server provides HTTP services in sync with the current HTTP standards.
This package provides the following functionalities:
* Install and uninstall apache HTTP server on a Windows platform.
* Manage apache HTTP server: Start, Stop and Restart.
* Execute any apache command on server.

=Supported versions=
Apache HTTP Server version 2.4

=Limitations=
(none)

=Setup=
* Oracle JRE 1.7 or higher must be installed on Agent OS and "java" must be set as executable on the same.
* To run the action on Windows, Apache HTTP server executable httpd must be present on the corresponding agent OS.
* To run the action on UNIX, apachectl script must be present on the corresponding agent OS.
* Required configuration file(s) for HTTP Server must also be present on agent OS.

=Variables=
PCK.AUTOMIC_APACHE_HTTPSERVER.PUB.VARA.PACKAGE_PARAMETERS
* DEFAULT_SERVICE_NAME: Windows service name to be used when user does not specify one in promptset while running actions on windows agent. The default value is apache2.4

=Actions=

Following actions are supported:
* Action Name: PCK.AUTOMIC_APACHE_HTTPSERVER.PUB.ACTION.INSTALL_SERVICE_WINDOWS
* Action Description: This action installs the Apache HTTP server as a service on windows.

* Action Name: PCK.AUTOMIC_APACHE_HTTPSERVER.PUB.ACTION.UNINSTALL_SERVICE_WINDOWS
* Action Description: This action uninstalls the Apache HTTP server installed as a Windows service.

* Action Name: PCK.AUTOMIC_APACHE_HTTPSERVER.PUB.ACTION.START_SERVER
* Action Description: This action starts Apache HTTP server.

* Action name: PCK.AUTOMIC_APACHE_HTTPSERVER.PUB.ACTION.STOP_SERVER
* Action Description: This action stops the Apache HTTP server gracefully.

* Action Name: PCK.AUTOMIC_APACHE_HTTPSERVER.PUB.ACTION.RESTART_SERVER
* Action Description: This action restarts the Apache HTTP server.

* Action Name: PCK.AUTOMIC_APACHE_HTTPSERVER.PUB.ACTION.EXECUTE_COMMAND
* Action Description: This action runs any ad hoc apache http command.]]></DOC>
</DOCU_Docu>
</DOCU>
</uc-export>